SK

SATHISH KUMAR

Professional Summary

Energetic Sales Representative offering demonstrated success identifying prospects and converting leads into customers. Superior communication skills with ability to understand client needs and close sales. Recognized for creativity and resourcefulness in meeting and exceeding sales, revenue and profit goals. Bringing 2 years of related experience.

Work History

Yantros India Private Limited-Sales Manager(08/2022 to Current)

Onboarding T1&T2 Restaurants , Key account Management, Team Handling, Data Monitoring, CRM

Business Development Manager (08/2019 8/2022)

Netambit (Swiggy -Bundl Technologies)

Handling Cities

Rajapalayam,Nagercoil,Kanyakumari, Pudukkottai,Thiruvarur,Ramanadhapuram

Mighty Bites - Franchise Manager Dharmapuri, TN 07/2018 - 08/2019

- Monitoring 4 outlets In Tamilnadu
- Worked with Mighty Bite Manager to resolve The problems And improve operations and provide exceptional customer service.

Corrotech Building Maintenance - Part Of The MCT Group Of Companies - BMS Coordinator Dubai, Dubai

06/2016 - 06/2018

Supervised 5 Buildings and 2 Villa in providing excellent customer service to callers requiring assistance for Day to day issues.

NTC LOGISTICS INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED - CES - Site Engineer

Chembarambakkam, TN

12/2014 - 06/2016

- Worked with Gamesa Wind (madhya pradesh khandala) customers to understand requirements and provide exceptional Logistic service.
- Worked with Gamesa Wind (kalyandurg rajasthan) customers to understand requirements and provide exceptional Logistic service.

Like2mailsathish@gmail.com 636 926 0813 489/5, Ramachandrapuram, Agraharam, Pudukkottai, TN 622001

Skills

- Staff training
- Field Study
- Business growth
- Onboarding
- Retention strategies
- Product promotions
- Network development
- Operations monitoring
- Closing techniques
- User training

Education

11/2014

Shanmuganathan Engineering College Arasampatti, TN

Bachelor of Engineering Technology:

Computer Science

Computer Science Engineering

• Graduated with 65% GPA

Subramanian Polytechnic College

Rayavaram, TN

High School Diploma

Diploma Computer Science Engineering

• Graduated with 79% GPA